<resources>
    <string name="app_name">First Step</string>
    <!--Personal details activity strings-->
    <string name="first_name_edit_text_hint">Please Enter Your First Name</string>
    <string name="surname_edit_text_hint">Please Enter Your Surname</string>
    <string name="age_label_text_view">Please Enter Your Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="name_age_label">
        Please enter your information so our service can be personalised just for you.
    </string>

    <!--Contact activity strings-->
    <string name="contact_label">
        We just need to gather some contact information to ensure we can get in touch with you.
        \nYou can choose to be contacted by both email and phone if you want.
        \nIf you don\'t want to be contacted by either email or phone leave them blank.
    </string>
    <string name="email_edit_text_hint">Please Enter Your Email Address</string>
    <string name="email_checkbox_label">I would like to be contacted by email</string>
    <string name="phone_edit_text_hint">Please Enter Your Phone Number, including country code</string>
    <string name="phone_checkbox_label">I would like to be contacted by text</string>
    <string name="complete_registration_button">Complete Registration</string>

    <!--Confirmation activity strings-->
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="confirm_email_text">
        The last step is to confirm your email address and then you\'re good to go.
        \n Make sure you\'re details are correct before requesting the corfirmation link!
    </string>
    <string name="confirm_phone_email_text">
        The last step is to confirm your phone number and email address and then you\'re good to go.
        \n Make sure you\'re details are correct before requesting the corfirmation email and text!
    </string>
    <string name="confirm_phone_text">
        The last step is to confirm your phone number and then you\'re good to go.
        \n Make sure you\'re details are correct before requesting the corfirmation code!
    </string>
    <string name="send_phone_confirmation_button_text">Send me a confirmation text!</string>
    <string name="send_email_confirmation_button_text">Send me a confirmation email!</string>
    <string name="confirm_name_label">Name :</string>
    <string name="confirm_dob_label">Date of Birth :</string>
    <string name="confirm_email_label">Email :</string>
    <string name="confirm_phone_label">Phone :</string>

    <string name="enter_ver_code_hint">Enter Verification Code</string>
    <string name="send_another_text">Send Text Again</string>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>There are far, far better things ahead than anything we leave behind - C. S. Lewis</item>
        <item>But in the end one needs more courage to live than to kill himself - Albert Camus</item>
        <item>The bravest thing I ever did was continuing my life when I wanted to die - Juliette Lewis</item>
        <item>When it is darkest, we can see the stars - Ralph Waldo Emerson</item>
        <item>Believe in yourself and all that you are. Know that there is something inside you that is greater than any obstacle - Christian D. Larson</item>
        <item>Never let anyone else decide who you are - Caroline Rhea</item>
        <item>We either make ourselves miserable, or we make ourselves strong. The amount of work is the same - Carlos Castaneda</item>
        <item>Place your hand over your heart, can you feel it? That is called purpose. You\'re alive for a reason so don\'t ever give up - unknown</item>
        <item>If you are looking for a sign not to kill yourself, this is it - unknown</item>
        <item>All things are difficult before they are easy - Thomas Fuller</item>
        <item>Grit your teeth and let it hurt. Don\'t deny it, don\'t be overwhelmed by it. It will not last forever - Harold Kushner</item>
        <item>Never never never give up - Winston Churchill</item>
        <item>The longer we dwell on our misfortunes, the greater is their power to harm us - Voltaire</item>
        <item>Don\'t cry because it\'s over; smile because it happened - Dr. Seuss</item>
        <item>Suicide is not a remedy - James A. Garfield</item>
        <item>Though no one can go back and make a brand new start, anyone can start now and make a brand new ending - Carl Bard</item>
        <item>When the whole world is silent, even one voice becomes powerful - Malala Yousafzai</item>
        <item>Suicide is a permanent solution to a temporary problem - Phil Donahue</item>
        <item>If you want to show me that you really love me, don\'t say that you would die for me, instead stay alive for me - unknown</item>
        <item>Never give up, for that is just the place and time that the tide will turn - Harriet Beecher Stowe</item>
        <item>If someone listens, or stretches out a hand, or whispers a word of encouragement, or attempts to understand a lonely person, extraordinary things begin to happen - Loretta Girzartis</item>
        <item>I hope you live a life you are proud of. If you find that you are not, I hope you have the strength to start all over again - F. Scott Fitzgerald</item>
        <item>The world is a better place with you in it - unknown</item>
        <item>If your heart is still beating, God is not done with you yet - Dillon Burroughs</item>
        <item>The pain passes, but the beauty remains - Pierre August Renoir</item>
        <item>Suicide doesn\'t end the chances of life getting worse, it eliminates the possibility of it ever getting any better - unknown</item>
        <item>I wanted to kill the sweetest,smartest and the most beautiful person on this earth, but then I thought..SUICIDE is a crime! - unknown</item>
        <item>One of the secrets of life is to make stepping stones out of stumbling blocks - Jack Penn</item>
        <item>The real reason for not committing suicide is because you always know how swell life gets again after the hell is over - Ernest Hemingway</item>
        <item>The man who kills a man kills a man. The man who kills himself kills all men. As far as he is concerned, he wipes out the world - G.K. Chesterton</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
